Okay, why creating a bookmark, let extension have a new feature. So I've had a new scripts in this video
So go to the main page
You pre-port few services that I will show you how we can actually use
So there's like extension source viewer. I will just do it on an extensive team. So as you can see
I can view source online
So this is about Pinterest how you can get stars or stimuli defined there
So if I copied it over and view source
I will get some information directly from here from the extension. So I see background
And all of the code and if you want to look at inspire the build bookmark it based in that extension
It actually can do it for yourself. So because now if you copy here
I want to have a
Bookmark wallet that will reveal steam ID
You can go back again
And
You see this copy ID
And all the stuff all right, so let me the first task I press enter
Opening agent
Now we go back
I can up in now. Epic games look up where I can try to look for something so
Epic account ID
I want to have a
Bookmarklet that will
New you
I pick ID
User
I'll go to another extension. We have an Xbox game tag. So this will like try to look for
each profile
It's a good for his books tracker
PSN profiles when you can verify that user exists
Some resolvers it's like a local website, so you can try to add another one
And so you can get like a profile group page ID for Facebook. I will ask it in the third agent
I want you to create a script for Facebook
Structure
And let's button this will go back again
And this will be a tiktok as you can see
I can copy the image
From that authenticate. I really recommend that website. You can create a bookmarklet based on that
So another one will be here as you can see the image was uploaded
Is that image to see
How you can extract ID from tiktok
And write me and book
Markle for this and I will create a new chat. That's great
And after it's been creating our create a new agent because now if I go to my bookmarklet
As you can see I have a lot of things obviously. I can always spin them up to favorites and everything
But I will mess and change so now just
Take it off. I don't want to use it. So I will turn it off
And pin
Enter it off now
And what I'm going to do I want to choose a username and a user ID transitor's
Risk photo. So I will just go again and see if I don't have a Twitch. I think I don't have so to open new agent
Which ID? Thanks structure
Now open new agent and now we implement a few features
So please change
pin
From favorite
Bookmarklets
functionality
To a star
That will help us to add it to
favorites and now I will implement and want
To narrow
Down some of categories
Let's make it more
Unpackable third instruction we could probably ask a new agent add a search bar
Where I can quickly look up
Marklet the top
The top
So I have free clear extractions as you can see I have created a book market for steam ID
And then I would test it out before actually releasing that extension. We see some of it here
So in pop up we see another code
This is the steam finder and let me see actually
Steam finder as we see it create a like a script directly here
Or the border. So we will test it out for everything
All right, oh, it's really fast creating extension is pretty fast now
And now if I go back to my
How can you so just train this mr. Tiv and now we'll just go and operate up first. I will update when it's done
I can go and look for some so there is a search bar if I type steam
I see social media and steam ID finder. I see the star
So now there is a star and I can remove it
So it will not be found. No, I see the community ID. So if I try to look for something like
steam ID
I'll just look for random account if I type it now here and I will just go to steam
So chamedia steam finder we get all of the IDs
Legacy and profile your little end was made
In just few seconds our task is now to test it out
I think you could change a little bit design because it's not so
easy to read
but as you can see you can
Visual visual calls
Hello pace remove JavaScript copy all links to clipboard
So this is a like links that I can copy if I go back here
And there are some webtoos reverse whiz. So if I go reverse whiz it will just allow us to pop up the address
There is like web intelligence drop text on
You can always put like this and it will just directly go
And there is a possibility for debugging like some quick overlay
and sometimes
I will just go back again because this one is one protected
So as we can see we applied some text so quick team text
Some external resources by domain nice nice nice
Now we see outline box moving specter
How try to play it again
Okay inspect
And we see actually
The active class and it's high forage class. That's great
Nice that is canceled now. So I can use external resources script
So we see all of the resources in the text. That's pretty great and it creates the green nice
We can remove styles
As you can see open selection google text the speech
Mr. Tef
So actually it works directly from him you can translate as a new button
So you do just open
In translation mode and no worries if I refresh it will go back
There are some other stuff like general you may find there
No image found
Okay, copy all links in clipboard extract emails
I think I saw that clip put everywhere
Okay extract emails on page but no one has been found but
If we go to one of the pages like this scene at maybe he'll be able to find some
In my founder I see already email find around this
And we can obviously extend from that
Couple links power to try to compare because as you can see you have a email finder and extra emails on page
Okay, I can remove it this one
Extract email on page quick list
So I'm going to go back
extract email on
I will just copy the row fast and now we'll go back again
It says that it stays on
And yeah, I think it's great
And obviously we can try to toggle some code modes
Give that in mind this we can have some similarities like
This is reading productivity and there's like a dark mode again. I think it runs that current page
This is the status election
Okay
This stuff in great. There's a content discovery display all links correct that count
We get like characters yet. This is what I remember I added it because we had like a word count as well
Yeah, right there
If I go back to another country and you go to another link and try to look for correct account
If I go back and tap it again content directory
I will see I can
Word frequency search
Yeah, this one is like to see for example
File and we can check on forwarding occurrences, so that's great
And I think this character display all images into this go. Okay, first we didn't have to go to this and you're all images
And we have only images directly from here
And that's pretty great
And I think it's that's it as we can see you have a lot of things in
Steam or Twitch, so there is no Twitter username, but if I go like
So I think
This is a popular Twitch streamers
I go to Twitch tracker
And there's one profile and if I go now and open like social media
And here we can get like
To which I will ask to make it alphabetically, but as you can see this Twitch extractor
And because it's not his profile, but rather profile on Twitch tracker, we have to go to official profile
So this is the official profile and now go all I can quickly type it to each
And
Now we just go this and we see the username and profile
And everything that was used for that obviously it's actually the same but sometimes it can vary
Sometimes it can be different. So that's great. So the last prompt it will be new agent
It's a nice collection
But I want you to sort scripts
Up on that take way in each category
And another engine will be the question press control that as well like get that you might
Please
Tell me
if
scripts and categories
are right
And there are no
duplicate
similar scripts in this
Bookmarker extension
It
It has been added so I will go back to next action or open
Not to each user name, but manage extension. I'll paint it up
Now as you can see everything is pretty nice
Fire so
Try to execute and I'll go back because the first one. I think there was a question
Recommendation to remove a bit remove a state to English supports. Okay. These are recommendations
Please
recommendations
Okay, I need to remove the duplicate of it and just one more until it's chasing
This one is removed this one is removed
Actually, it's from the main file. Some of these are like extracted scripts. It's validating can
Be able to get some of it here
As you can see it removed now this has not duplicate or a similar scripts and
What I'm going to do now is going to refresh and now it's
Pre-clear until you can get some of it here. So everything is nice. This is actually in like a wide mode
So if you want to use it more often
And what is reading right?
So if you type now dark mode
You can easily
Invert visual colors here